Hunting Grounds is a action, thriller film directed by Derek Barnes.
Desperate to find refuge for her children, Chloe Marvino runs away from her Mafia tied
husband, and finds shelter in a cabin with a recluse drifter named Jake.
But as her husband's henchmen draw closer to her, it turns out
that Jake is the biggest enemy of them all.
Chloe, played by Emily Alatalo.
Jake, played by Tim Rozon.
Mick, played by Patrick Garrow.
Vincent, played by Jon McLaren.
Zach, played by Milton Barnes.
Carl, played by Mikaël Conde.
This article lists characters and actors in the Predator franchise.
The original series consists of five films, Predator (1987), Predator 2 (1990),
Predators (2010), The Predator (2018), and Predator: Badlands (2025).
One prequel Prey (2022) and one animated film Predator: Killer of Killers (2025), as well as the
video games Predator: Concrete Jungle (2005) and Predator: Hunting Grounds (2020).
The series revolves around mankind's deadly
encounters with the Predators (Yautja).
The tone is intense.